inspiringsavings.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy

## **Inspiring Savings Respects Your Privacy**

This privacy policy sets out how _ **Inspiring Savings Media**_ uses and protects any information that you give while using www.inspiringsavins.com

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit[ InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[, ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Inspiring Savings Media** may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from date.

### **What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

We may receive information about you from other sources. You may link your website account in your comments or user profile on [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[. ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)If you choose to leave a comment or link your website account in your user profile or comments, we will receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account.

### **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * To operate and maintain[ InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize this website according to your interests.
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of[ InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) and customize [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) for your account.
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts.
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries.
  * To provide you with user support.
  * To track and measure advertising on [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against the unauthorized or illegal activity.

  * **Anonymous Data**

From time to time, we may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

  * **Third-party Use of Personal Data**

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information. Additionally,   may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

[InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) currently uses the following third-party service providers:

_**Favado**_ – this service is used to create deal lists at chain stores around the nation.  Please refer to Favado’s privacy policy for further information.

_**Google Analytics**_ – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/). Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

_**MailChimp**_ – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications. Please refer to MailChimp’s privacy policy for further information.

**_Social Fabric Analytics From Collective Bias_ – **this service tracks traffic information on select sponsored posts.  Please refer to Social Fabric’s privacy policy for further information.

**_Social Warfare_ – **this service tracks shares throughout users social media accounts (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram & Google) and provides counts on shares on [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/). Please refer to Social Warfare’s Privacy Policy for more information

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended solely at this website’s [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

  * **  Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL, Verizon, Spectrum, etc), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Chrome or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site

  * **Cookies  and Web Beacons**

**A cookie** is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

_**You can choose to accept or decline cookies**_. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

  * **Automatically-Collected Information**

We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/). For example, when you use [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[ ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/).[ ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)We may also collect information about actions you take when using  [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[ ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)such as links clicked.

We also use third party advertisements on [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[ ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)to support this website. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Mediavine or Google through Google Adsense) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

  * **Publicly Visible Information**

If you create a user profile on [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[ ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible. To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation. Your email address will never be available publicly. Users may see your username, profile description, and website information.

### **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### **Advertising**

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you to duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

**Display Ads**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) which may use cookies, as discussed above.

• **Retargeting Ads**

Occasionally [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter or Instagram, in order to market [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)

• **Affiliate Program Participation**

[InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) If you click on a link from an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

• **Newsletters**

On [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) you may [subscribe to one or all our current newsletter,](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/newsletter-subscription/) via MailChimp which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. This also allows [InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)[ ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

### **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

  * **  Sensitive Information**

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to  [InspiringSavings.com. ](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/)This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, home address, telephone numbers, or any type of memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

**• Children’s Information**

[InspiringSavings.com](https://www.inspiringsavings.com/) does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16.

I can always be reached for Privacy Policy questions by [emailing me directly!](mailto:Jen@inspiringsavings.com)

### **Opt-Out**

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us. You can also contact opt out directly to any of these [third-party advertisers here. ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed)

**_Thank You for visiting!_**
